Guide to the Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
- Drawings, 1924-2004
  - North Ridge Country Club (Tube 278)
    Halcan, Corley & Associates Inc; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - North Ridge Country Club (Tube 179)
    Grading plan, landscape plan
    Leif Valand & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Northwestern Halifax County High School, 1970-1975 (Tube 705)
    Pregrading Plans, Schematic Site Plan, Overall Site Plans, Revised Overall Site Plans, Site Plans, Schematic Site Study, Plot Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Davis Charles C. Jr. AIA; Halifax County (N.C.)
  - Northwestern Halifax County High School, 1975 (Tube 833)
    Pregrading Plan
  - Northwestern Mutual Insurance Co. (Tube 51)
  - Northwestern Mutual Insurance Co., 1962 (Tube 52)
  - Novak (Richard L. and Laura K.) residence, 1998 (Tube 455)
    Master Landscape Plan, Plat of Subdivision
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Orange County (N.C.)
  - O'Hanlon (Mr. and Mrs. Ike) property (1 of 2), 1967 (Tube 644)
    Renovation details and lighting diagram
  - O'Hanlon (Mr. and Mrs. Ike) property (2 of 2), 1967 (Tube 829)
    Gazebo Details, Enlarged Plans and Details, Master Landscape Plan
  - Office building, 1980 (Tube 229)
    Plans and elevations, site development
    Bell Design Group; Nags Head (N.C.)
  - Office building, 1981 (Tube 231)
  - Office building for Alex Bowness, 1985 (Tube 534)
    Preliminary Site Plan, Final Grading and Landscape Plan, Lighting Plan
  - Office building for Alex Bowness, 1992 (Tube 533)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Moore County (N.C.)
  - Office building for General Telephone Company of the Southeast, 1967 (Tube 720)
  - Office building for John D. Latimer & Associates (1 of 2), 1965 (Tube 263)
    Planting plan, details
    John D. Latimer & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Office building for John D. Latimer & Associates (2 of 2), 1965 (Tube 264)
    Staking plan, site plan
  - Office building for John Loving & Company, 1994 (Tube 539)
  - Office building for The Coble Diary Products Co-Operative, Inc., 1964 (Tube 732)
    Details, Landscape Plans and Details
  - Office facility for Victor Comptometer Corp., 1968 (Tube 707)
    Preliminary Site Plan, Site Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Mideastern Construction Co.; Durham County (N.C.)
  - Offices for Dees, Dees, Smith, Powell, and Jarrett, 1975 (Tube 698)
    Plant List, Details and Notes, Planting Plan, Grading and Storm Drainage, Staking Plan, Construction Details, Preliminary Site Development Plan, Site Plans
  - Offices for Dees, Dees, Smith, Powell, and Jarrett (Tube 731)
    Preliminary Site Development Plan, Property Map
  - Ol' Miner No. One, 1973 (Tube 829)
  - Old Farm House, 1974 (Tube 468)
    Floor layout; Elevations
    Shook and Torlton Investment Co.; Falcone John
  - Old Fort Macon Family Campgrounds (1 of 2), 1973 (Tube 718)
    Preliminary Plans, Elevations
  - Old Fort Macon Family Campgrounds (2 of 2), 1973 (Tube 769)
  - Old Fort Macon Family Campgrounds (Tube 731)
  - Olde Towne Section I, 1976 (Tube 532)
  - Orange County aerial photograph (Tube 684)
  - Orange County Board of Education: Schools and facilities, 1962 (Tube 829)
    Staking and Grading, Typical Details
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Orange County orthophoto maps, 1985 (Tube 585)
    Aerial Photograph with Map
    L. Robert Kimball & Associates; Orange County (N.C.)
  - Orange County orthophoto maps (Tube 457)
    Aerial maps
    Robert Kimball & Associates; Orange County (N.C.)
  - Orange County Health Center (Tube 828)
    Details, Preliminary Site Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Jesse M. Page & Associates; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Orange County schools and facilities, 1962 (Tube 648)
  - Oriental-American Folk Museum (1 of 2), 1999 (Tube 507)
    Wish Plan
  - Oriental-American Folk Museum (2 of 2), 1999 (Tube 556)
  - Our Lady of Grace (1 of 2), 1979 (Tube 298)
    Conceptual landscape plan
  - Our Lady of Grace (2 of 2), 1979 (Tube 303)
  - Paden (Jim and Jane) residence, 1980 (Tube 14)
  - Page (Mr. and Mrs. William S.) residence (1 of 2), 1972 (Tube 8)
  - Page (Mr. and Mrs. William S.) residence (2 of 2), 1972 (Tube 17)
    Kinston (N.C.)
  - Pappagallo Shop (Tube 351)
  - Park Symbol: Commerce Park, 1964 (Tube 57)
  - Parker Hannifin Corporation Facility (Tube 749)
    Bell Design Group; Hillsborough (N.C.)
  - Parker Hannifin Corporation Facility, 1985 (Tube 751)
    Irrigation plan, planting plan, site plan
  - Parrish residence, 2003 (Tube 90)
  - Parrish (Anne K.) residence (1 of 2), 1993 (Tube 90)
    Preliminary landscape, master plan
  - Parrish (Anne K.) residence (2 of 2), 1993 (Tube 91)
    Preliminary landscape plan, master plan
  - Paul (Mr. and Mrs. Noel A.) residence (Tube 283)
  - Paul (Mr. and Mrs. Noel A.) residence, 1980 (Tube 291)
  - Pawleys Island Presbyterian Church, 1989 (Tube 746)
    Site Plans, Details, Planting Plan
    Key Architecture, PA; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Pawleys Island (S.C.)
  - Peace College, 1977 (Tube 137)
  - Peace College, 1979-1986 (Tube 198)
    Davidson residence Hall, Harp Street Parking Area, site and planting plan
  - Peace College, 1982-1985 (Tube 252)
    Proposed site improvements, site plan
  - Peace College, 1986 (Tube 813)
    Campus irrigation system
  - Peace College, 1982-1991 (Tube 204)
    Site and planting plan, proposed site improvements
  - Peace College, 1979-1982 (Tube 530)
    Proposed Site Improvements, Proposed Signage, Site Plans Existing Conditions, Topographic Survey, Plan Maps, Plan and Details
    John A. Edwards & Company, Consulting Engineers; Bell Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Peace College, 1977-1985 (Tube 852)
    Proposed Improvements to State Property South of the Campus, Proposed Site Improvements - Harp and Peace Street Modifications, Site Plan, Planting Plan, Aerial Photograph, Map
    Bell Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.) Planning Department; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Peace College, 1977-1984 (Tube 848)
    Master Development Plans, Site Map, Existing Conditions, Proposed Improvements to State Property South of the Campus, Proposed Site Improvements - Harp and Peace Street Modifications, Construction Details, Site Plans, Study No. 3: Site and Building Relationships with Blount Streetscape
    McKimmon, Edwards, and Associates; Bell Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Peace College, 1965 (Tube 130)
    Parking lot
  - Peace College, 1964-1971 (Tube 118)
    Site work adjacent to proposed music building, tennis court area, landscape plan, master development plan phase 2, landscape plan phase 4, staking plan, master development plan phase 1, landscape plan phase 2
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell Design Group; McKimmon and Rogers; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Peace College, 1968-1980 (Tube 529)
    residence hall, campus development
    Bell Design Group; McKimmon and Rogers; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Peace College, 1978 (Tube 890)
  - Peace College, 1991 (Tube 892)
  - Peace College: Athletic complex, 1983 (Tube 527)
  - Peace College: Davidson residence hall, Harp-Peace Streets area, 1979-1991 (Tube 531)
    Site Plans, Planting Plans, Proposed Site Improvements, Parking Area and Lighting, Irrigation Plan and Details, Construction Details
  - Peace College: President's residence (1 of 2), 1976 (Tube 710)
    Staking and Grading Plan, Site Plan
    Bell Design Group; McKimmon, Rogers, Edwards, & Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Peace College: President's residence (2 of 2), 1976 (Tube 722)
    Planting and Grading Plan, Details, Plant List and Planting Notes
  - Peden Steel Company, 1967 (Tube 710)
  - Peed Drive Development (Tube 853)
  - Pembroke State University, 1986-1988 (Tube 356)
    Pedestrian quadrangle, 12 year plan, campus plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Pembroke (N.C.)
  - Pembroke State University, 1989 (Tube 114)
    Pedestrian quadrangle
  - Pembroke State University: Pedestrian quadrangle (Tube 170)
  - Pembroke State University: Police building, 1988 (Tube 110)
    Preliminary sketch, site plan
    Pembroke (N.C.)
  - Pentecostal Holiness Church topographic survey, 1988 (Tube 572)
    Surveying Associates Inc.; Garner (N.C.)
  - Pepsi-Cola Marketing Center, 1975 (Tube 722)
    Schematic Landscape Plan, Construction Details, Planting Plan, Plant List, Details, and Planting Notes, Grading and Storm Drainage, Details and Elevations, Staking and Lighting Plan
  - Perry (Dr. and Mrs. Cary) residence, 1973 (Tube 7)
    Bell Design Group; Louisburg (N.C.)
  - Perry (Dr. and Mrs. Cary) residence (Tube 710)
  - Pilot Mountain State Park, 1970 (Tube 680)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Yadkin County (N.C.); Surry County (N.C.)
  - Pilot Mountain, Stone Mountain (Tube 44)
    Surry County (N.C.)
  - Pilot Views: A planned community in Pilot Mountain, 1985 (Tube 304)
    Bell Design Group; Pilot Mountain (N.C.)
  - Pinehurst Branch: Fayetteville NC Stake, 1985 (Tube 445)
    Site Plans, Irrigation, Details, Plantings Sedimentation & Erosion Plan
    Phillips & Associates, Architects; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Pinehurst (N.C.)
  - Pinehurst Plantation (Tube 229)
  - Pinehurst Plantation (Tube 552)
  - Pitt County Mental Health Center, 1975 (Tube 457)
    Dudley & Shoe Architects; Garden Gallery; Greenville (N.C.)
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence (1 of 5), 1987 (Tube 370)
    Furniture placement, furniture and lighting, elevations, foundation plan, floor plans
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence (2 of 5), 1987 (Tube 371)
    Floor plans, topographic survey, building elevations, site plan, lighting plan
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence (3 of 5), 1987 (Tube 372)
    Floor plans, site plans, building elevations, flooring diagram and lighting plan
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence (4 of 5), 1987 (Tube 373)
    Elevations, foundation plan, floor and lighting plan, site plan
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence (5 of 5), 1987 (Tube 374)
    Floor plans, site plan, building elevations
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Tube 90)
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Tube 439)
    Topographic Survey, Site Plans, Elevations, Foundation Plan, Ground Floor, Main Living Floor, Irrigation Plan
    Bell Design Group; Freehold Land Surveys, Inc.; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Durham (N.C.)
  - Pitt (Daniel and Claudia Bloom) residence, 1988 (Tube 137)
    Site plan alternate rear yard design
  - Planning Study: Greendale (Tube 29)
  - Plant Training Center GTE (Tube 256)
  - Plastina (Frank and Connie) residence, 2001 (Tube 144)
    Triangle Residential Designs Inc.
  - Plaza at Jail Building and Law Enforcement Center, 1967 (Tube 164)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Graves & Toy; Freeman-White Architects, Inc.; Charlotte (N.C.)
  - Plaza West: Friden Inc. and Victor Comptometer Building (Tube 712)
    Development Study
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham County (N.C.)
  - Plaza West Complex (Tube 843)
    Mirlein, Inc., Developer; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Pleasants (Robert and Margaret) residence (Tube 529)
    Proposed planting
    Bell Design Group; Bayleaf (N.C.)
  - Poole (Lonnie and Carol Lynne) residence (1 of 3), 1991 (Tube 15)
  - Poole (Lonnie and Carol Lynne) residence (2 of 3), 1991 (Tube 55)
  - Poole (Lonnie and Carol Lynne) residence (3 of 3), 1991 (Tube 298)
    Site development plan, landscape plan
  - Poole (Mr. and Mrs. Lonnie C., Jr.) residence, 1991 (Tube 756)
    Landscape plan, site survey
  - Poole (Mr. and Mrs. Lonnie C., Jr.) residence (Tube 761)
  - Pope Crossing Subdivision, 1986 (Tube 859)
    Preliminary Plat, Site Plan, Development Plan for Pope Road Subdivision and Crystal Oaks Townhomes
    Ballentine Associates PA; Cimarron Capital, Inc.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Pope's Crossing (1 of 2), 1987 (Tube 854)
    Main Entrance Planting Plan, Entrance Elevations, Typical Planting Strip, Planting Plan
  - Pope's Crossing (2 of 2), 1987 (Tube 868)
    Main Entrance Planting Plan, Typical Planting Plan
  - Pope's Crossing at Five Oaks, 1987 (Tube 161)
    Entrance signage, details, elevations, plans
  - Porter (Katherine and Frederick) residence (1 of 2), 1998 (Tube 471)
  - Porter (Katherine and Frederick) residence (2 of 2), 1998 (Tube 455)
    Site Development Plan, Plat Plan, Interior Elevations and Wall Sections, Renovations Elevations, Renovation Floor Plan, Foundation Plan, and Site Plans, Staking and Grading
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Smart-Isley Architects Inc.; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Porter (Katherine and Frederick) residence, 1997 (Tube 470)
    Plat Plan, Foundation Plan, Renovation Plan, Renovation Elevations, Interior Elevations
    Smart-Isley Architects Inc.; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Powell Place, 1993-1994 (Tube 178)
    Master development plan, Pittsboro North land use plan, site plan, preliminary plan
    William C. Piver & Associates; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Pittsboro (N.C.)
  - Powell Place, 1994 (Tube 182)
    Entrance sign plan
  - Powell (Charles C.) property, 1988 (Tube 731)
    Joseph T. Johnston and Associates, Inc.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Price (Bob and Mary Jane) residence (1 of 2), 1983 (Tube 54)
  - Price (Bob and Mary Jane) residence (2 of 2), 1983 (Tube 301)
    Landscape plan, staking plan
  - Price (Bob and Mary Jane) residence (Tube 303)
  - Project "X" (Tube 697)
    Site plans and elevations for a 20-Unit Motel, restaurant, and shops
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham County (N.C.); Orange County (N.C.)
  - Property of Columbus, Incorporated, 1968-1969 (Tube 730)
    Land Use Studies, Site Development Study for Phase One Area, Subdivision Development Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Bassett (Va.)
  - Property of Jefferson Pilot, 1985 (Tube 834)
    Property Map
    Marvin L. Borum and Associates; Guilford County (N.C.)
  - Proposed Carteret Civic Convention Center, 1976 (Tube 648)
    Landuse breakdown
  - Proposed Carteret Civic Convention Center (Tube 690)
    Maps of Emerald Isle, Cross Sections
  - Proposed Community Business and Office Center: Central Carolina Properties (Tube 571)
  - Proposed Community Business and Office Center: Central Carolina Properties, 1988 (Tube 572)
    Preliminary landscape plan, preliminary site plan
  - Proposed Halifax County Courthouse Square, 1974 (Tube 255)
    Master plan concept
    Davis Charles C. Jr. AIA; Bell Design Group; Halifax (N.C.)
  - Proposed Motel: Salter Path Road (Tube 35)
    Pine Knoll Shores (N.C.)
  - Prototypal Housing Module (Tube 257)
    Elevations, floor plans, master plan
  - Prototypal Housing Module (Tube 718)
  - Prototype Shelter (Tube 297)
    Plans and elevations, development plan
  - Prototype Solar Greenhouse, 1978 (Tube 447)
    Landscape Development Plan, Site Plans
    Latimer John D.; Bell Design Group; Martinsville (Va.)
  - Prototype Solar Greenhouse, 1977 (Tube 448)
    Foundation Plan, Floor plan, Sections and Details, Elevations, Solar Panel Array, Equipment Room and Sections, Site Plan, Drawing Index
  - Proud (Paul) residence (1 of 2), 1966 (Tube 17)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Orange County (N.C.)
  - Proud (Paul) residence (2 of 2), 1966 (Tube 7)
  - Providence Village for Ervin Industries, Inc., 1967 (Tube 36)
  - Providence Village for Ervin Industries, Inc., 1967-1968 (Tube 712)
    First Phase Development Rough Grading Plans, Site Plan
  - P.T.A. Headquarters Building: NC Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1960 (Tube 710)
  - Puglia (Sam and Linda) residence, 1985 (Tube 748)
    Staking, grading, planting plan, landscape plan
  - Puglia (Sam and Linda) residence (Tube 761)
  - Pullen Park (Tube 320)
  - Pullen Park, 1979-1989 (Tube 400)
    City of Raleigh zoning map, electrical site plan, aerial photograph, area south of railroad, property map, master plan, topographic map
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Bell Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Pullen Park, 1979-1989 (Tube 401)
    Carousel area improvements, water service to carousel house, study north of rail road, site development plan
  - Pullen Park, 1979-1989 (Tube 402)
    Site development plan, study of ramped deck near swimming pool, property map, railroad track planning
  - Pullen Park, 1973 (Tube 640)
    General development plans first phase, master plans
  - Pullen Park, 1972-1990 (Tube 318)
    Details, sedimentation and erosion control, staking and grading, contour map
  - Pullen Park: City of Raleigh Department of Parks and Recreation (1 of 3), 1973 (Tube 41)
  - Pullen Park: City of Raleigh Department of Parks and Recreation (2 of 3), 1973 (Tube 42)
  - Pullen Park: City of Raleigh Department of Parks and Recreation (3 of 3), 1973 (Tube 43)
  - Pullen Park: City of Raleigh Department of Parks and Recreation, 1988-1991 (Tube 76)
    Phase VI construction, master plan, planting
  - Pullen Park: City of Raleigh Department of Parks and Recreation, 1990-1991 (Tube 80)
    phase VI construction, details
  - Pullen Park: City of Raleigh Department of Parks and Recreation, 1988 (Tube 89)
  - Pullen Park: Master plan (Tube 840)
    Enlarged Maps, Study South of Railroad, Study North of Railroad-Parking Areas, Section of Railroad Spikes
  - Pullen Park: Phase III construction, 1978 (Tube 459)
  - Pullen Park: Phase VI construction, 1981-1989 (Tube 837)
    Enlarged Topographic Map, Area North of Railroad, Area South of Railroad, Existing Children's Playground, City of Raleigh Zoning Map, Suggested Construction for Railroad Trestle Superstructure
    Raleigh (N.C.) Planning Department; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.) Department of Parks and Recreation; Allan Herschell Company; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Pullen Park: Phase VI construction (1 of 2), 1990 (Tube 317)
    Staking and grading, planting, details
  - Pullen Park: Phase VI construction (2 of 2), 1990 (Tube 319)
  - Pulte Homes (Tube 442)
    Withers and Ravenel; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Quarter Deck: River Bend Plantation, 1973 (Tube 35)
  - Ragland (Mr. and Mrs. Trent, Jr.) residence, 1985 (Tube 686)
    McKimmon, Edwards, Hitch Architects; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Ragland (Mr. and Mrs. Trent, Jr.) residence, 1986 (Tube 756)
    Irrigation plan, planting, terrace area, staking and grading, lighting
  - Raleigh, 1981 (Tube 363)
  - Raleigh Area: Edwards Mill Road to Glen Eden Road (Tube 442)
    Site Plans and Overlays
  - Raleigh Civic Center: North Carolina sports show, 1982 (Tube 508)
  - Raleigh Department of Planning, 1981 (Tube 446)
    Landmark Engineering Co., Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh Department of Planning, 1968-1991 (Tube 451)
    Raleigh Urban Thoroughfare Study, Topographic Maps, Landscape rendering, Aerial Photographs, Planimetric & Topographic Map
    Bell Design Group; Harland Bartholomew and Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh map, 1969 (Tube 529)
  - Raleigh map (Tube 595)
    Topographic and Street Map Showing Capitol Area
  - Raleigh maps (Tube 431)
    Topographic maps, surveys
  - Raleigh maps (Tube 432)
    Property maps, surveys
  - Raleigh maps (1 of 2), 1997 (Tube 543)
    Topographic Plat Map
  - Raleigh maps (2 of 2), 1997 (Tube 544)
  - Raleigh Planning Department, 1984 (Tube 539)
    Aerial Photograph, Property Map
    Greenhorne & O'Mara, Inc; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh property maps, 1967-1991 (Tube 582)
    Full Grid Map, Individual Grid Maps, Street Maps
    Piedmont Aerial Surveys, Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.) Planning Department; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh Racquet Club, 1976-1977 (Tube 127)
    Staking, plant list, grading and storm drainage, site development
  - Raleigh Racquet Club, 1976 (Tube 130)
  - Raleigh Racquet Club, Inc., 1959-1973 (Tube 798)
    Site Plans, Cedar Ridge Development Contour Survey, Survey, Topographic Map, Preliminary Lighting Plan, Stadium Court Plan
    Russum C. W.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh Racquet Club, Inc., 1971-1975 (Tube 800)
    Site Plans, Landscape Plan Details, Grading Plans, Planting Plans, Preliminary Staking Plan
    Bell Design Group; Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh Savings and Loan Association, 1962 (Tube 282)
    Preliminary alterations
    Williams F. Carter Fred Carter 1913-2000; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh topographic map, 1988 (Tube 172)
  - Raleigh topographic map, 1981 (Tube 892)
  - Raleigh topographic map and property map, 1981-1984 (Tube 433)
  - Raleigh topographic maps, 1981-1988 (Tube 583)
    Topographic Map Sheets: 494, 552, 523, 551, 377, 495, 276, 297, 299, 283
    Greenhorne & O'Mara, Inc; Ragsdale Consultants, PA; Raleigh (N.C.) Planning Department; Landmark Engineering Co., Inc.; Carolina Aerial Mapping Service Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh: Wilmington Street parking deck (1 of 2), 1990 (Tube 156)
    Wilbur Smith Associates, Inc.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Raleigh: Wilmington Street parking deck (2 of 2), 1990 (Tube 157)
  - Ramblewood Subdivision, 1962-1963 (Tube 67)
    General plan; Mr. and Mrs. William S. Ward, owners
  - Randleman Lake (Tube 663)
    Water Critical Area Boundary Map
    Black & Veatch; Piedmont Triad Regional Water Authority; Guilford County (N.C.); Randolph County (N.C.)
  - Raychem Corporation, 1980-1982 (Tube 300)
    Tobacco barn historic area, lawns and planting, general landscape revisions
    Bell Design Group; Fuquay-Varina (N.C.)
  - Raychem Corporation, 1992 (Tube 316)
    Warehouse facility, unidentified plans
    Haskins, Rice, Savage & Pearce, PA; Fuquay-Varina (N.C.)
  - Raychem Corporation, 1979 (Tube 313)
    Site plan, site grading plan, paving and drainage plan, site utility plan, erosion control plan, miscellaneous details, roadways, planting details
    Lockwood-Green, Architects Engineers; Fuquay-Varina (N.C.)
  - Raychem Corporation (Tube 115)
    Quadrants A-E
    Bell Design Group; Greene Lockwood; Fuquay-Varina (N.C.)
  - Raychem Corporation, 1986 (Tube 167)
  - Raychem Corporation, 1979-1991 (Tube 315)
    Sanitary sewer profile, miscellaneous details, site utility plan, paving and drainage plan, general landscape revisions, topographic map
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion, 1989-1990 (Tube 377)
    Revised master plan, floor plans
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (1 of 7), 1990 (Tube 376)
    Site plan, grading/drainage/sediment/erosion control, floor plans
    Haskins, Rice, Savage & Pearce, PA; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Fuquay-Varina (N.C.)
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (2 of 7), 1990 (Tube 403)
    Site plan, map of base points, letter of transmittal
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (3 of 7), 1990 (Tube 192)
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (4 of 7), 1990 (Tube 194)
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (5 of 7), 1990 (Tube 293)
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (6 of 7), 1990 (Tube 312)
    Courtyard grading, irrigation, staking, planting, demolition, general site plan
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (7 of 7), 1990 (Tube 193)
    Site work package
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (1 of 3), 1990-1991 (Tube 284)
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (2 of 3), 1990-1991 (Tube 314)
    Courtyard irrigation, planting, construction details, landscape planting plan, site staking
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion (3 of 3), 1990-1991 (Tube 285)
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion, 1991 (Tube 292)
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion design development submittal (1 of 2), 1990 (Tube 378)
    Cover sheet, revised master plan, building plan, floor plans, elevations, building sections, wall sections
  - Raychem Corporation: Phase 2 expansion design development submittal (2 of 2), 1990 (Tube 379)
    Wall section, roof plan, stair plans, R&D process lab, shared open bay lab, environmental tanks and ovens, mpm training lab, speed shop, model shop enlarged plan, lab plans, chemical storage
  - RDU Center: RDU Airport (1 of 3), 1994 (Tube 410)